byoaudio.com 2003-08-01

# BYOBroadcast: Privacy Policy

BYOBroadcast is committed to customer service and we intend to continue that tradition by providing a private and secure browsing experience at BYOBroadcast. The following policy will help you to understand how we will treat your personal information. As we continue to improve our site and as we take advantage of developments in technology, this policy may change from time to time so please check this policy on an ongoing basis for revisions and updates.Information Collection and Use  
BYOBroadcast collects information from our web site in several ways. During registration, BYOBroadcast asks for information such as your name, email address, zip code and/or other information. Once you have submitted this information and chosen a valid password, you will be able to take full advantage of everything BYOBroadcast has to offer. You may also be asked for personal information when you report a problem with our site, or services; or, if you otherwise contact BYOBroadcast. Of course, we will require credit card information, as well as billing information when you establish a BYOBroadcast account.

BYOBroadcast also collects information using cookies, which are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. This information allows us to automatically link our customers to their personalized accounts. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. Please check your browser's guidelines should you wish to prevent cookies.

BYOBroadcast is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. **We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.** Information is collected with the sole purpose of providing BYOBroadcast services.

Information Disclosure   
When you are on the BYOBroadcast site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with only BYOBroadcast, its agents and representatives. BYOBroadcast will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. BYOBroadcast may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) BYOBroadcast's rights or property, other BYOBroadcast users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. BYOBroadcast will comply with the requests of all recognized legal entities to aid in the stopping of spam, distribution of illicit sexual content to minors, or any other illegal activity brought to our attention through such channels. 

BYOBroadcast may occasionally send you e-mail about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Only BYOBroadcast (or agents or representatives working on behalf of BYOBroadcast) will send you these emails. You may unsubscribe from the service information updates without any future correspondence or questions by sending an email to sbupdates@BYOBroadcast.com with "unsubscribe" in the subject line of the message. 

Your Contacts  
All contacts associated with your account are your property and BYOBroadcast has no title or authorization to use them in any way except as instructed by you. In the event that your account lapses with contact information in it, BYOBroadcast may automatically delete any and all contacts in your account within twenty-one (21) days of such lapse, and will notify you prior to doing so by email.

Your contacts are kept separate from those of other BYOBroadcast subscribers and at no time is information about your contacts shared with any other subscribers, affiliates or partners.

Due to the actions of a given contact, any number of BYOBroadcast customers may have the same contact in their account. However, a separate copy of each contact is kept for each BYOBroadcast customer and at no time is information about such "common" contacts shared or co-mingled.

Links  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
